<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<map 
	name="testmap" 
	version="1.0" 
	xmlns="tocsdb.html" 
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" 
	xsi:schemaLocation="tocsdb.html xml.xsd ">
	
  <spawnTerrorists>			map.gate1				</spawnTerrorists>
  <spawnCounterterrorists>	map.voctrainCellar		</spawnCounterterrorists>
  <bombPoint>				map.caf					</bombPoint>
  
  <root type="Node">
  	<refID>	map		</refID>
    <id>	map		</id>
    <desc>
    	THIS ELEMENT SHOULD BE INVISIBLE
    </desc>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.caf				</refID>
    	<id>	Employee Cafeteria	</id>
    	<name>	buttery				</name>
    	<name>	mess hall			</name>
    	<name>	cafeteria			</name>
    	<desc>
    		The employee cafeteria is completely deserted. Some of the wooden tables are 
    		upset and the meals of the escaped employees are spread over the ground. The
    		cold wind drifts small pieces of paper through the opened main entrance. A
    		passage behind the cofferoom leads upstairs to some offices.
    		This cafeteria seems to be the ideal place for the terrorists to plant the 
    		bomb.
    	</desc>
    	
    	<west>	map.beforeCaf		</west>
    	<up>	map.passOffice		</up>
    </node>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.passOffice		</refID>
    	<id>	Pass Office			</id>
    	<name>	office				</name>
    	<name>	issuing office		</name>
    	<desc>
    		The pass office of Airbus' site Manching is a small room above the cafeteria.
    		Here is enough space for about five employees to work on issuing problems. 
    		Some of the computers are not switched of, one of the workers has even forgotten
    		to lock its PC.
    	</desc>
    	
    	<down>	map.caf				</down>
    </node>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.beforeCaf		</refID>
    	<id>	In Front of the Cafeteria</id>
    	<name>	square				</name>
    	<desc>
    		You're on the open space in front of the cafeteria, which hulks up in the
    		east. The open door invites you to escape from the icy wind that waves debries
    		and pieces of paper from left to right.
    		In the west, the passage between to office buildings opens into a wide crossing.
    	</desc>
    	
    	<west>	map.crossing		</west>
    	<east>	map.caf				</east>
    </node>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.crossing		</refID>
    	<id>	Crossing			</id>
    	<desc>
    		You're on a wide crossing, leading from the employee cafeteria in the east to
    		both, the barracks in the east and the great black ventilation block in the
    		north.
    	</desc>
    	
    	<north>	map.ventilation		</north>
    	<west>	map.barracks		</west>
    	<east>	map.beforeCaf		</east>
    </node>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.barracks		</refID>
    	<id>	At the Barracks		</id>
    	<desc>
    		You're at the passage leading past the EF Assembly Line hall to the vocational
    		training center in the west. Around you, there are low-rise containers with
    		engineering offices inside. Between two containers in the north, a route leads
    		over the celt's wall. To the east, the passage opens into a wide crossing.
    	</desc>
    	
    	<west>	map.lake			</west>
    	<east>	map.crossing		</east>
    </node>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.lake			</refID>
    	<id>	Extinguishing Pond	</id>
    	<desc>
    		You're at the extinguishing pond in front of the vocational training center,
    		which hulks up to the west. The bleak wind creates smooth waves on the dark,
    		grey water.
    		To the east, a small gap between the abandoned cars opens into a passage,
    		leading to the engineering containers.
    	</desc>
    	
    	<west>	map.voctrain		</west>
    	<east>	map.barracks		</east>
    </node>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.voctrain		</refID>
    	<id>	Vocational Training Center</id>
    	<desc>
    		This is the first floor of the vocational training center of Airbus' site 
    		Manching. On the wall on the right hand side, there are numerous notices,
    		including the menus currently selled in the employee cafeteria.
    		From here, you can go downstairs, to the building's cellar, upstairs, to
    		visit the vocational training advisor's offices and west, to leave the
    		building.
    	</desc>
 		
 		<node type="Node">
 			<refID>	map.voctrain.notice	</refID>
 			<id>	Cafeteria Menu		</id>
 			<name>	notice				</name>
 			<name>	menu				</name>
 			<name>	plan				</name>
 			<name>	menu plan			</name>
 			<desc>
 				"Cafeteria is closed today due to terroristic attacks."
 			</desc>
 			<weight>1					</weight>
 		</node>
 		
 		<west>	map.lake			</west>
 		<up>	map.voctrainOffice	</up>
 		<down>	map.voctrainCellar	</down>
    </node>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.voctrainOffice	</refID>
    	<id>	Advisor's Offices	</id>
    	<desc>
    		You're in the office of two Airbus DS employees which are vocational
    		training advisors, as the sign outside the room states. There are two
    		desks in the center of the room and desk chairs on both sides. In the left
    		corner, there is a big chest.
    		The only way leads downstairs.
    	</desc>
    	
    	<node type="Node">
    		<refID>	map.voctrainOffice.sign	</refID>
    		<id>	Identification Sign		</id>
    		<name>	label					</name>
    		<name>	sign					</name>
    		<name>	notice					</name>
    		<desc>
    			"Christian Eckl - CHOG2; Francois Maurice - CHOG2;"
    		</desc>
    	</node>
    	
    	<node type="LockableNode">
    		<refID>	map.voctrainOffice.chest</refID>
    		<id>	Large Chest				</id>
    		<name>	chest					</name>
    		<name>	box						</name>
    		<name>	big chest				</name>
    		<desc>
    			This is a large, old chest, strengthened with stainless steel.
    		</desc>
    		
    		<node type="Node">
    			<refID>	map.voctrainOffice.chest.maurice</refID>
    			<id>	Francois Maurice				</id>
    			<name>	francois						</name>
    			<name>	maurice							</name>
    			<name>	person							</name>
    			<desc>
    				Inside the chest, you can see a medium aged man, clothed with a ironed
    				shirt and shoulder-lengthened dark hair. He looks surprised at you.
    			</desc>
    		</node>
    		
    		<closed>	true				</closed>
    		<locked>	true				</locked>
    		<key>		map.voctrainCellar.key	</key>
    	</node>
    	
    	<down>	map.voctrain		</down>
    </node>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.voctrainCellar	</refID>
    	<id>	Cellar				</id>
    	<desc>
    		You're in the cellar of the vocational training center. A flickering flouroscent
    		tube creates an anxious atmosphere in the passages which formerly led to the 
    		employee's showers on the left hand side and the snack room on the right hand
    		side. Daylight falls in from upstairs.
    	</desc>
    	
    	<node type="Node">
    		<refID>	map.voctrainCellar.key	</refID>
    		<id>	Golden Key				</id>
    		<name>	key						</name>
    		<desc>
    			The golden coating chips already off and reveals the corroded iron, the
    			heavy key is actually made of. 
    		</desc>
    		<weight>1						</weight>
    	</node>
    	
    	<up>	map.voctrain				</up>
    </node>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.ventilation		</refID>
    	<id>	Ventilation Cube	</id>
    	<desc>
    		Near the huge, black ventilation cube of building 361, two paths join into one,
    		leading to the wide crossing in the south. The first one comes from Gate 1 in 
    		the north, the second comes past the cube from building 632 to the northwest. 
    		Warm steam streams out of the ventilation system, swirled by the piercing wind.
    	</desc>
    	
    	<north>	map.gate1			</north>
    	<south>	map.crossing		</south>
    	<west>	map.before362		</west>
    </node>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.before362		</refID>
    	<id>	At Building 362		</id>
    	<desc>
    		You're on the square before building 362, the huge engineering building which's
    		glass front hulks up in the west. By the route that leads eastwards to the 
    		site's main entrance, the small Foodbox container in the north exhales the 
    		mouth-watering smell of warm snacks. To the south, a tiny bridge spans over the
    		celt's wall and a road branches southeastwards to building 361's ventilation
    		cube.
    	</desc>
    	
    	<north>	map.foodbox			</north>
    	<south>	map.barracks		</south>
    	<east>	map.gate1			</east>
    </node>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.foodbox			</refID>
    	<id>	Foodbox				</id>
    	<desc>
    		You're inside the site's northern foodbox. No humans can be seen, but a beef
    		and pork loaf (as consumed very often in souther parts of Germany, as well as
    		in Austria) exhales a tasty smell from inside an oven. In the shelves next to 
    		the exit in the south, a cold pretzel with butter can be found.
    	</desc>
    	
    	<node type="Node">
    		<refID>	map.foodbox.pretzel	</refID>
    		<id>	Pretzel				</id>
    		<name>	butter pretzel		</name>
    		<desc>
    			This is a perfectly shaped pretzel, scattered with salt nuggets and
    			coated with chives-refined butter.
    		</desc>
    		<weight>1					</weight>
    	</node>
    	
    	<node type="OpenableNode">
    		<refID>	map.foodbox.oven	</refID>
    		<id>	Oven				</id>
    		<name>	furnace				</name>
    		<name>	cooking				</name>
    		<name>	stove				</name>
    		<desc>
    			This little oven is used to bake southern Germanie's traditional beef
    			and pork loafes in the foodbox. It's currently switched of.
      		</desc>
      		
      		<node type="Node">
      			<refID>	map.foodbox.oven.leberkas	</refID>
      			<id>	beef and pork loaf (as typically consumed in souther parts of Germany as well as in Austria and the Switzerlands) </id>
      			<name>	beef and pork loaf			</name>
      			<name>	loaf						</name>
      			<name>	leberkas					</name>
      			<name>	leberkäse					</name>
      			<desc>
      				Yummy.
      			</desc>
      			
      			<weight>3							</weight>
      		</node>
    	</node>
    	
    	<south>	map.before362		</south>
    </node>
    
    <node type="Room">
    	<refID>	map.gate1			</refID>
    	<id>	Gate 01				</id>
    	<desc>
    		You're at gate 01 of Airbus DS site Manching, which is the main entrance
    		to the plant. An ice-cold wind causes a decent rustling of leaves in the 
    		distant trees. The street through the entrance leads southwards to a 
    		massive black ventilation system. A cobbled path branches in the west to 
    		building 362.
    	</desc>
    	
    	<south>	map.ventilation		</south>
    	<west>	map.before362		</west>
    </node>
  </root>
  
</map>
